UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Audio-Visual Collection
1968-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000 AV
15.56 cubic feet
15.6 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
Audio recordings of music and moving images
7682224
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 09, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, November 02, 2015
Scope and Contents
Film, video, and audio recordings of music, including long time Vice President and Legislative Department Head Evelyn Dubrow, other union leaders, and covers issues such as diversity, worker strikes, working conditions, sweatshops including Kathy Lee Gifford interviews and pieces on Nike and Gap, Ann Hoffman on prison labor, NAFTA, and clothing imports.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000/007 AV: UNITE Legislative Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/012 AV: UNITE Northeast Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/022 AV: UNITE Education Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 AV: UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/026 AV: UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs Audio-Visual Materials 6000/037 AV: UNITE Communications Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/050 AV: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/056 AV: UNITE Boston Joint Board Audio-Visual Materials 6343 AV: Leonard Greenwald Collection of UNITE Audio-Visual Materials
Textile industry, New York (State), New York; Textile workers, Labor unions, New York (State), New York; Sweatshops, New York (State), New York; Clothing trade, New York (State), New York; Clothing workers, Labor unions, New York (State), New York; Gifford, Kathie Lee, 1953-; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Textile Workers Union of America; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7682224
- Evy Dubrow Roast - February 26, 1997, 10 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  6000 AV #13
- Viewer call-in program - Tuesday 9/27/1994, 11 (Box 1)
  6000 AV #11
- El Paso Sweatshops - Unpaid Workers - Prime Time Live, ch.7, 3/14/1991, 12 (Box 1)
  6000 AV #15
- Fox Morning News 6/28/1996, 13 (Box 1)
  6000 AV #16
- FPI, CBS News 12/20/1990; Evy on Fast Track FOX News 5/8/1991, 14 (Box 1)
  6000 AV #17
- Fenton Communications; GAP and NIKE: No Sweat, 1 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #18
- Sweatshops - K L Gifford - DATELINE, WNBC-TV/Ch 4, 2 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #19
- Larry King Live - CNN, 3 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #20
- Al Gore at Legislative Conference, Washington, DC 5/18/1993, from Antonio Osea, 4 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #21
- PBS GUESS piece, 5 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #22
- Interview with Ann Hoffman - WNBC, Today Show, 5/20/1994, 6 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #23
- Ann Hoffman Prison Labor Testimony, May 24, 1999, Judiciary Sub Cmte, 7 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #24
- ILGWU, Multishop: Join In, 4/28/1988, 8 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #25
- ILGWU - News Closed -Up - WPIX-TV (IND) New York, June 19, 1993, 9 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #26
- Its About Jobs - ILGWU, 1994; 10 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #27
- Immigration/Virginia Coughlin, May 24, 1996, 11 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #28
- Lane Kirkland Memorial Service - 9/23/1999, 12 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #29
- Lane Kirkland Memorial Service, 9/23/1999, 13 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #29 (copy 2)
- Medal of Freedom Presentations, 8/11/1999, 14 (Box 2)
  6000 AV #30
- Mickey Mouse Goes to Haiti: Walt Disney and the Science of Exploitation, 1 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #31
- The True Cost of NAFTA, 2 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #32
- The True Cost of NAFTA - ILGWU, 7/28/1993, 3 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #33
- ILGWU: One Strike and You're Out!, 4 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #34
- ILGWU: One Strike and You're Out!, 5 (Box 3)
- Fletcher and Rowley Consulting, Henry Strauss, Our Choice, 6 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #35
- Restoring Employee Rights is Good for America, 7 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #36
- Mathew Schoenwald: Interview on Medicare Catastrophic, Sept. 28, 1989, 8 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #37
- AFL-CIO Issue AD Save, 9 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #38
- CBC Newsworld, Rough Cuts, The Suit War, Aired March 10, 1997, 10 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #39
- Stop Sweatshops!, 11 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #40
- Stop Sweatshops!, 12 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #40 (copy 2)
- TJ MAX, Evansville, Ind., Teamster L218, 13 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #41
- ILGWU/Triangle Shirt Waste Fire Anniversary, March 25, 1992, 14 (Box 3)
  6000 AV #42
- This Week with David Brinkley; Featuring: Kenneth Lipper, Irwin Kellner and Robert Rubin, April 3, 1994, 1 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #43
- Union Workers, Newshour with Jim Lehrer, PBS; Sweatshops, CBS Sunday Morning, WCBS, 2 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #44
- UNITE! Because Every Vote Counts, 3 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #45
- 1997 USHLC Highlights Video, 4 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #46
- News Programs, 1990; 5 (Box 4)
  1.Eyewitness News, WABC-TV/NYC, 3/6/1990; 2.Channel 2 News, WCBS-TV/NYC, 3/6/1990; 3.News 4 New York, WNBC-TV/NYC, 3/26/1990; 4.Channel 9 News, WWOR-TV/NYC, 3/26/1990; 5.News 4 New York, WNBC-TV/NYC, 3/26/1990 --- 6000 AV #47
- Clothing Worker; Imported Clothing, 1/28/1988, 6 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #48
- Immigration and Naturalization Service, Office of Employer and Labor Relations: Complying with the New Immigration Law, 7 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #49
- Coverage, CWA/ILGWU, CWA-105, 7/21/1993, 8 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #50
- Domsey Workers, You are the Union, 9 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #51
- El Monte Workers Lawsuit, September 5, 1995, Los Angeles Coverage, 10 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #52
- Fenton communications: GAP and NIKE: No Sweat, 11 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #53
- The Garment Industry: News from City Hall, WNYC-TV, November 8, 12 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #54
- Hard Copy, three-part series on Nicaraguan sweatshops, November 1997, 13 (Box 4)
  6000 AV #55
- Paula Green Advertising ILGWU; Health Care - 3/18/1994, 1 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #56
- ILG Convention 1989, 2 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #57
- Is There a Sweatshop in Your Future?, 3 (Box 5)
  English/Spanish - 6000 AV #58
- Kathie Lee Fashions/Sweatshops Fines and Backpay: New York Coverage, July 11, 1996, 4 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #59
- Lane Kirkland Memorial Service: C-Span Videotape 152308: part 1 of 1, 5 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #60
- Jay Mazur, ILGWU, 6 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #61
- Pillowtex, Video 2, 7 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #62 (2nd copy)
- We Do the Work: Sewing Our Future, 8 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #63
- Stepan Chemical: the Poisoning of a Mexican Community, 9 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #64
- UNITE for Dignity!, 10 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #65
- 1994 United States Hispanic Leadership Conference, 11 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #66
- Zoned for Slavery, 12 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #67
- CBS Evening News: Sweatshops, 13 (Box 5)
  6000 AV #68
- House Ways and Means: Textile and Footwear Quotes, 5/17/1987, 3 (Box 6)
  6000 AV #73
- ILGWU-NY Labor Day Parade -, 4 (Box 6)
  6000 AV #69
- AH Productions - Crafted With Pride; Made in USA/Miss America, 5 (Box 6)
  6000 AV #70
- Italics: the Italian American Magazine; Episode #34, 6 (Box 6)
  6000 AV #74
- Kathie Lee Gifford/SEO Fashions Sweatshop, May 23, 1996, 7 (Box 6)
  6000 AV #75
- Interview with Jay Mazur, October 10, 1990, 8 (Box 6)
  6000 AV #76
- ILGWU/ACTWU Merger: NY Network coverage, Feb. 20-21, 1995, 9 (Box 6)
  6000 AV #77
- Jay Mazur Interview, 10 (Box 6)
  6000 AV #78
- Lane Kirkland Tribute, 11 (Box 6)
  6000 AV #79
- Lane Kirkland Tribute (copy 2), 12 (Box 6)
- Hillary Clinton visits with Garment Workers - 3/6/1996, 1 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #80
- Evy Duty, 2 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #81
- ILGWU Dept. of Labor Hall of Fame 1993, 1990; 3 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #83
- China Trade Deal/Protesters; Crossfire, Cable News Network, April 12, 2000, 4 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #82
- Paula Green Advt., ILGWU; Health Care, 3/23/1994, 5 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #85
- Amalgamated Bank "New Go", 6 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #84
- Ellis Island Medals of Honor Ceremony and Dinner - Part 1, October 27, 1986, 7 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #87
- The Golden Door, presented by the New York Joint Board, ACTWU, 8 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #86
- We Do the Work, Show 309, Sewing Our Future, 9 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #89
- Ellis Island Medals of Honor Ceremony and Dinner - Part 2, October 27, 1986, 10 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #88
- Future Shop: A Modular Manufacturing Shop, 11 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #90
- Future Shop: A Modular Manufacturing Shop, 12 (Box 7)
  6000 AV #90 (copy 2)
- Unions - New York Close Up, New York 1 News, January 17, 1993, 1 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #91
- Gospel Seder A Jewish/African-American/Christian Passover Freedom Service, Part I, 2 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #92
- Herman Starobin, Tape, 1,2,3 and 4, 3 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #93
- ABC 20/20 Monday the Shame of Saipan, May 24, 1999, 4 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #94
- Free Trade with Mexico, Panel II (Dubrow), 3/14/1991, 5 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #95
- Ellis Island: Medals of Honor, July 3, 1993, 6 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #96
- Dinkins Endorsement, 3/15/1989, 7 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #97
- The Golden Door, National PBS Broadcast, 8 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #98
- Regis/Commercial/Miss America, 9 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #99
- Kathie Lee Gifford/Sweatshops, New York, Network and Cable Coverage, May 23-24, 1996, 10 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #100
- NY is fashion, ILGWU, August, 1992, 11 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #101
- Muzafer Christi, Metroline, re: Immigration, 4/11/1987, 12 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #102
- Crafted with pride in USA, Inside Opinion, 12/22/1992, 13 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #103
- Ellis Island medals of Honor, May 21, 1995, 14 (Box 8)
  6000 AV #104
- Triangle Shirt-Waist Fire Anniversary, March 25, 1994, 1 (Box 10)
- Struggle at Domsey, 2 (Box 10)
- Proposed Merger, Today in NY WNBC TV, February 1, 1995, 3 (Box 10)
- Paula Green Advertising, ILGWU, Health Care, 3/18/1994, 4 (Box 10)
- AFL-CIO, ACTWU/ILGWU, UNITE Press Conference, Tapes 1-3, 5 (Box 10)
- UNITE, Word, Face, TRT, 01/24/1996, 6 (Box 10)
- Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1995; 7 (Box 10)
  Miami Beach, Florida, June 29-30, 1995
- 1995 UNITE Convention Highlights, 8 (Box 10)
- ILGWU TB Study, Local NYC Coverage, Oct. 19-20, 1992, 9 (Box 10)
- Full Show, Boy Meets World, 3/17/1995, 10 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Chorus, AFL-CIO Convention, 11/1989, 11 (Box 10)
  Washington, DC
- New York is Fashion -- 7/14/1992, 12 (Box 10)
- The Vanishing Sun, episode on Sweatshops, 13 (Box 10)
- Garment Workers, 14 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Round-Up Presentation, 1995 Convention, 15 (Box 10)
  20 Years of Look for the Union Label
- Hillary Clinton Sews Union Label, 3/6/1996, New York City, 16 (Box 10)
- Segment on illegal sweat shops, Channel 2 News at 11, 4/28/1993, 17 (Box 10)
- Sweatshops - UPN 9 News, 10/9/1995, 18 (Box 10)
- People get ready: UNITE Southern Region 1997, 19 (Box 10)
- Inside Edition, 20 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Fire Drill/Rally, News Conference, 3/27/1991, 21 (Box 10)
- Triangle Fire Anniversary (1988), WABC, 3/25/1988, 22 (Box 10)
- UNITE!: Stop Sweatshops Campaign, December, 1996, 23 (Box 10)
- Triangle Fire Anniversary, News Coverage - 1990 -- 3/26/1990, 24 (Box 10)
- Triangle Fire Anniversary - 3/25/1992, Vocal New York Coverage, 25 (Box 10)
- ILGWU w/Nelson -- Solidarity Day 1991 ILGWU Chorus, 26 (Box 10)
- NY 1992 Fashion Show in Central Park, 27 (Box 10)
- Working Solutions: Work vs. the Family, Rutgers University, 28 (Box 10)
- CBS Sunday Morning, 10/20/1991, 29 (Box 10)
- Leaving home we do the work, 30 (Box 10)
- ILGWU/ACTWU Merger, NY Network Coverage - Feb. 20-21, 1995, 31 (Box 10)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union - Media Coverage of June 1989 Convention, 32 (Box 10)
- Segment with Susan Cowell of ILGWU, 5/27/1993, 33 (Box 10)
- Segment on sweat shops, 4/29/1993, 34 (Box 10)
- NY is fashion, August 1992, 35 (Box 10)
- UNITE! Stop Sweatshops Campaign, December, 1996, 36 (Box 10)
- UNITE! Presentation, 9/20/1995, 37 (Box 10)
- My name is Mary Brown, 38 (Box 10)
- 9/16/1986 - Homework Hearings, 1 (Box 11)
- ILGWU - 1.Paula 2.Anna 3.Doctor, 2 (Box 11)
  Spanish
- ILGWU - 1.Comparison 2.Promises 3.Strike 4.Betting, 3 (Box 11)
- ILGWU Voter registration, 4 (Box 11)
- Jay Mazur, Susan Meisinger, 5 (Box 11)
- ILGWU - 1.Conversation Radio 2.Trabajador Elsa 3.Trabajador Hippolito 4.Trabajador Awilda 5.Trabajador Carmen, 6/27/1990, 6 (Box 11)
- ILGWU-, 1989; 7 (Box 11)
  1.Berta I 2. Berta II 3.Carmen I 4. Carmen II 5.Pablo 6.Hipolito I 7.Hipolito II 8.Latinos 9.Street -- 11/9/1989
- ILGWU - 1.Olmos 2.Carmen III - 11/29/1989, 8 (Box 11)
- ILGWU Voter Registration -- 6/23/1989, 9 (Box 11)
- ILGWU Apparel Jobs Abroad - 9/27/1992, 11 (Box 11)
- ILGWU - Union Label Song from the Nanny - 1/18/1995, 12 (Box 11)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union - Its about jobs, 13 (Box 11)
- UNITE - Words, Face - 1/26/1996, 14 (Box 11)
- Leslie Fay Rally, NYC, 9/22/1993, 15 (Box 11)
- We do the work, Sewing our future, 16 (Box 11)
- We do the work, Show 309, Sewing our future, 17 (Box 11)
- Future Shop: a modular manufacturing shop, 18 (Box 11)
- ILGWU: UNITE and Fight, 19 (Box 11)
- ILGWU: Apparel Job - 9/30/1992; Maidenform - 9/29/1992, 20 (Box 11)
- Count me in - a bridge to citizenship -- 9/23/1994, 21 (Box 11)
- UNITE, Convention Program, 1995, 22 (Box 11)
- Paula Green Advt. - ILGWU - 4/26/1994, 23 (Box 11)
- ILGWU Dept. of Labor, Hall of Fame 1993 -- 3/9/1994, 24 (Box 11)
- ILGWU - Fashion Shows, 25 (Box 11)
- Construction Workers who renovated the theater, 1993; 26 (Box 11)
  Late Show with David Letterman - 9/30/1993
- UNITE/Jay Mazur - The Money Wheel - 7/11/1995, 27 (Box 11)
- Behind the Seems - 12/11/1994, 28 (Box 11)
- ILGWU - On the Move-- 6/1989, 29 (Box 11)
- ILGWU: UNITE and Fight, 30 (Box 11)
- Robert Reich - Garment Industry Labor Practices -- 9/14/1995, 31 (Box 11)
- Soho Fashions; USA Tonight, 32 (Box 11)
- Triangle Shirtwaist Fire Remembered by ILGWU - 3/27/1995, 33 (Box 11)
- Union Merger - UNITE! - June 30, 1995, 1 (Box 12)
  Nightly Business Report, PBS-TV Network -- 6000 AV #108
- 1995 UNITE Convention Highlights, 2 (Box 12)
- Convention of Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1995; 3 (Box 12)
- Tape of CBC's Liz Clairborne Segment, 4 (Box 12)
  6000 AV #109
- Medal of Freedom Presentations - 8/11/1999, 5 (Box 12)
  6000 AV #106
- Evy Duty, ILGWU, May 1989, 6 (Box 12)
- Challenges, 3/6/1995 - Should You Have to Join a Union to Keep Your Job?, 7 (Box 12)
- Pensions 2000: Ancient Lands, New Opportunities, Highlight Tape, 8 (Box 12)
  6000 AV #107
- American Institute for Free Labor Development: A Permanent people's Struggle, 9 (Box 12)
- Saipan Clothing Manufacturers; Follow Up Segment - 3/13/1998 and 3/20/1998, 10 (Box 12)
- UNITE: 2003 UNITE! Convention, 11 (Box 12)
- UNITE: 2003 UNITE! Convention, 12 (Box 12)
- Interview Sol Stetin, Twua Laeder: Oct. 10, 1995, Chicago, Ill., 13 (Box 12)
  Video Stan Rosen Rose Bud Video
- Labor at the Crossroads: No more Band-Aids: wring the Health Care Crisis, 14 (Box 12)
- ILGWU Chorus at Grand Central Station, Eyewitness News, 9/4/1992, 15 (Box 12)
- El Preston - ILGWU Spot, 16 (Box 12)
- Art Rodriguez, UFW, 17 (Box 12)
- Video from Seth M. Bodner, Exec. Dir., National Knitwear and Sportswear Ass., 18 (Box 12)
  apparel trade issue aired around the country on public television
- Sweatshops, 1992; 19 (Box 12)
  aired - 1/27/1992
- ILGWU - Composite video, 20 (Box 12)
- Paula Green Advertising, ILGWU - 3/18/1994, 21 (Box 12)
- Union Health Center, Animated Tour - April 1998, 22 (Box 12)
  6000 AV #105
- Future Shop: a Modular Manufacturing Shop, 23 (Box 12)
- Future Shop: a Modular Manufacturing Shop, 24 (Box 12)
- ILGWU, Apparel Job - 9/30/1992; Maidenform - 9/29/1992, 25 (Box 12)
- Its time for a Real Union! Its time for UNITE!, 1 (Box 13)
- Its time for a Real Union! Is time for UNITE!, 2 (Box 13)
- CBC News world - The Suit War - Aired March 10, 1997, 3 (Box 13)
- CBC News World - The Suit War - Aired March 10, 1997, 4 (Box 13)
- CBC News World - The Suit War - Aired March 10, 1997, 5 (Box 13)
- CBC News World - The Suit War - Aired March 10, 1997, 6 (Box 13)
- CBC News World - The Suit War - Aired March 10, 1997, 7 (Box 13)
- Ahora es el momento para una !UNION VERDADERA; !Ahora es el momento para UNITE, 8 (Box 13)
- Ahore es el momento para una !UNION VERDADERA; !Ahora es el momento para UNITE, 9 (Box 13)
- Hard Copy three-part series on Nicaraguan sweatshops, 1997; 10 (Box 13)
  November 1997
- Hearing on the Garment Industry Proviso (tape 1 of 2), 11 (Box 13)
- Hearing on the Garment Industry Proviso (tape 2 of 2), 1998; 12 (Box 13)
  8/6/1998
- UNITE for the future, 13 (Box 13)
  tape #1241
- NACA Protest at First Union; nine reports aired in Charlotte - 10/2/1995-10/3/1995, 14 (Box 13)
- Peerless media coverage - 1995, 15 (Box 13)
- Livelyhood #103-Honey We Bought the Company, 16 (Box 13)
- K-Mart Demo - 3/23/1996, Houston, TX, 17 (Box 13)
- CBC News World - The Suit War, 18 (Box 13)
- Organized Labor, CBS Sunday Morning, 19 (Box 13)
- Primetime - El Paso, 20 (Box 13)
- Organized Labor - CBS Sunday Morning, 21 (Box 13)
- NBS Nightly News 8/5/1993 - Worker Education Program, 22 (Box 13)
- Timecode for Kmart, Greensboro - 3/30/1996, 23 (Box 13)
- News Feature: 9/6/1997 Local Coverage - UNITE, 24 (Box 13)
- GUESS Jeans Labor Controversy - July 20, 1998, 25 (Box 13)
- GUESS Jeans Boycott - September 15, 1998, 26 (Box 13)
- News 25 Coverage - T.J. Maxx Stories, 27 (Box 13)
- Lichtenberg Ratification - 10-16-1991, 28 (Box 13)
  MASTER
- News Reports on Cone Mills ESOP, Cliffside, NC, October 1, 1990, 29 (Box 13)
- UAW in Belvedere #2 - Raw Footage, 30 (Box 13)
- Kmart Protest-Atlanta, 31 (Box 13)
- Mohawk Carpets and 60 Second Commercial, 1 (Box 14)
- Mohawk Carpets and 60 Second Commercial, 2 (Box 14)
- Mohawk Carpets and 60 Second commercial, 3 (Box 14)
- Springs Industries, Inc. - Bed Fashions, 4 (Box 14)
- Jobs with justice - tape #3, 5 (Box 14)
- Jobs with justice - Tape #2, 6 (Box 14)
- Jobs with justice - Tape #1, 7 (Box 14)
- Press Coverage Peerless - January 18, 1996, 8 (Box 14)
- Peerless - TV Coverage - 12/10/1995, 9 (Box 14)
- Peerless - TV Coverage - 12/10/1995, 10 (Box 14)
- Kmart Atlanta - Tape 1 - 3/23/1996, 11 (Box 14)
- Panville Healthtex, 12 (Box 14)
- CBS Nightly News - OSHA rules, 13 (Box 14)
- On the Move: Victory at 1199, 14 (Box 14)
- Crossfire - CNN - November 8, 1993, 15 (Box 14)
- Peerless Media - Coverage 1995, 16 (Box 14)
- UNITE Meeting -- 10/23 and 12/9/2000, 17 (Box 14)
- UNITE! News -- Kitchens Rally, 2/13/1997; Burdines, Aug. 1996, 18 (Box 14)
- LICHTO A (no other labeling), 19 (Box 14)
- LICHTO B (no other labeling), 20 (Box 14)
- UNITE! - Because every vote counts, 21 (Box 14)
- UNITE! - Because every vote counts, 22 (Box 14)
- Peerless - TV Coverage - 12/10/1995, 23 (Box 14)
- Kmart Atlanta Rally - tape #1 - 3/23/1996, 24 (Box 14)
- Americans Discuss Social Security, 25 (Box 14)
- Unlabeled, 26 (Box 14)
- Peerless/Sweatshops - Unite Rally Atlanta - AFL/CIO Footage, 27 (Box 14)
- 10-12 (no other labeling), 28 (Box 14)
- TJ MAXX - 2/16/1999 - Leaflet w/cops, 29 (Box 14)
- Made in the USA - 3/29/1992, 30 (Box 14)
- Mitch McConnell - November 4, 1998, 31 (Box 14)
- Cav's Corner - Detroit Newspaper Strike - 10/8/1996, 32 (Box 14)
- Mattan the Carpet - 6/26/1995, 33 (Box 14)
- Loehmanns/Union - January 26, 1999, 34 (Box 14)
- Going Global - News hour with Jim Lehrer - July 23, 1997, 1 (Box 15)
- Feccheimer - Meeting with Boss - tape 2 - 10/1/1998, 2 (Box 15)
- UNITE Protest against Peerless Clothing Company, 3 (Box 15)
- A Message from President Bruce Raynor - November 2001, 4 (Box 15)
- A Message from President Bruce Raynor - November 2001, 5 (Box 15)
- A Message from President Bruce Raynor - November 2001, 6 (Box 15)
- UNITE Campaign for the Future, 7 (Box 15)
  English version
- UNITE Campaign for the Future, 8 (Box 15)
- Surviving the bottom line with Hendrick Smith, 9 (Box 15)
- News Coverage of Jesse, Rally in NC - April 1996, 10 (Box 15)
- Cavanaugh's Corner -- 10/1996, 11 (Box 15)
- Organizing Institute Reports: 1.ABC-World News Tonight - 6/3/1993; 2.CNN - 6/8/1994, 12 (Box 15)
- Organizing Institute Reports: 1.ABC-World News Tonight - 6/3/1993; 2.CNN - 6/8/1993, 13 (Box 15)
- Atlanta CLC - October 1, 1998, 14 (Box 15)
- Jo-Ann Mort - 12/1/1995, 15 (Box 15)
- Kmart Protest - Norfolk - 3/23/1996, 16 (Box 15)
- Booted Out: We do the work, 17 (Box 15)
- UNITE, 18 (Box 15)
- Surviving the bottom line with Hendrick Smith, 19 (Box 15)
- NIKE Labor Practices, 20 (Box 15)
- UNITE Victory - 11/10/1999; Charlotte News Coverage, 21 (Box 15)
- (In) Visible Women, 22 (Box 15)
  English by Ellen Spiro and Marina Alvarez
- Satelite Child Care: The Future of Quality Daycare, 23 (Box 15)
- Columbia Teach-In, October 3-4, 1996; tapes 1 and 2, 24 (Box 15)
  Includes Betty Friedan, Richard Rorty, John Sweeney and Cornel West
- Union Protest at Sol Frank - 5/13/1998, 25 (Box 15)
- AFL-CIO Strategic Media Campaign - Sample Spots, 26 (Box 15)
- Anti-Sweatshop - 12/13/1996, 27 (Box 15)
- The Story of the K-Mart Workers - 2/1997, 28 (Box 15)
- CNN Coverage of Poultry Industry, 29 (Box 15)
- Civil Right Committee - Jan. 15-16, 1994, 30 (Box 15)
- Union Navy - 7/3/2001, 31 (Box 15)
- Paying to Lose Our Jobs - 9/27/1992, 32 (Box 15)
- Kmart Demo, 33 (Box 15)
- L.A. Sweatshops - CNN-TV, Headline News, 34 (Box 15)
- Life and Times (Wednesday Edition) - 10/7/1997, 35 (Box 15)
  GUESS Jeans/Latino Film Fest/Arts Cal
- Sweat Shops - 8/15/1994, 36 (Box 15)
- Protests Against Discrimination - 3/23/1996, 1 (Box 16)
- Made in China - May 10, 1994, 2 (Box 16)
- Discounted Lives, 3 (Box 16)
- ACTWU Press Conference 8/10, 4 (Box 16)
- Jesse Jackson visits Sanderson Farms, Hazlehurst Plant, 5 (Box 16)
- Atrium Action - 1/1998, 6 (Box 16)
- La Region del Rio Colca, 7 (Box 16)
- Saipan Clothing Manufacturers, 1998; 8 (Box 16)
  Edited Version; Follow Up Segment
- AFL-TV, RUSH, 9 (Box 16)
- Atlanta: Labor Law Reform Demonstration, 10 (Box 16)
- Columbia Teach-In, October 3-4, 1996, 11 (Box 16)
  tapes 5 and 6; Includes end of 2nd Plenary Session, Workshops
- Clinton in Louisville - 9/29/1992, 12 (Box 16)
- The Internationale, 13 (Box 16)
- Multiplan - Sy Syms Tribute Film, 14 (Box 16)
- CNM, Saturday, July 29th, Presentation, 15 (Box 16)
- AFL-CIO, 1991 Dickey, 16 (Box 16)
- News Hour with Jim Lehrer: Focus: Labor - 1999/10/12, 17 (Box 16)
- Gore in Miami - 99-002, 2/19/1999, Tape #2, 18 (Box 16)
- A Family Album, 19 (Box 16)
- Peerless - Atlanta Derr, 8/10/1996; Lord and Taylors and Macys, 20 (Box 16)
- Macy's - Atlanta Sweatshop Demo, Raw footage, 12/7/1996, 21 (Box 16)
- Sweatshop Protest, Macy's-Lenox Square-Atlanta - 12/7/1996, 22 (Box 16)
- Hoop Dreams, Sweatshops -- 12/7/1996, 23 (Box 16)
- ACTWU Press Conference -- 8/8/1994, 24 (Box 16)
- Donahue, October 6, 1992, 25 (Box 16)
- Concerned Citizens for Working Freedom, School teacher humiliation, 26 (Box 16)
- Cone Mills, Haw River -- 6/6/1991, 27 (Box 16)
- Kmart Newnan Captive, 28 (Box 16)
- OSHA -- CBS Evening News, ABC World News, 29 (Box 16)
- Marshall's Victory Party -- 6/1997, 30 (Box 16)
- Eden, 3 News Clips, Greensboro Rally w/Bruce, 31 (Box 16)
- Greensboro - 7/30/1997 - Postal/Sweatshop Action, 32 (Box 16)
- Sweatshop Rally, Macys -- 12/7/1996, Raw Footage, 33 (Box 16)
- Peerless Rally, Gaithersburg, MD - 1996, 34 (Box 16)
- AFL-CIO Medicare and Minimum Wage Spots - 6/26/1996, 1 (Box 17)
  1.Couple-Hayworth, 2.Lady-whitefield, 3.Wither-Flanagan, 4.Peace- Stockman
- The Metals-Anatomy of a union, 2 (Box 17)
- Behind the Seams, 3 (Box 17)
- Peerless Atlanta - 8/1996, 4 (Box 17)
- Union Celebration - 6/24/1999, 5 (Box 17)
- Workers Rights Hearing - Feb. 18, 1999; Miami at Caleb Center, 6 (Box 17)
- 60 Minutes - CBS - 9/27/1992; Nightline - ABC - 9/29 and 9/30, 7 (Box 17)